{
    "id": "84050989cf2a45de9c43fe03012648f4",
    "title": "Conjunctions Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Coming late, James tiptoed into the room —————— he should disturb the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lest",
                "unless",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I worked hard —————– I might win the first prize.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "so that",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She spoke in such a low voice —————- few could hear her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "as",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She was —————– weak that she could hardly stand.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That is Peter, —————– I am mistaken.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "unless",
                "provided that"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We will have plenty to eat ——————- that no uninvited guests turn up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "in order",
                "provided"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I will forgive you ——————– you don’t repeat the offence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lest",
                "if",
                "on condition that"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They were disappointed ——————- you weren’t in.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "as",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "There will be no trouble —————- you keep your mouth shut.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "whether",
                "so long as"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "——————– were his words and gestures that the listeners were hypnotized.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Such",
                "So",
                "As"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}